myfreecopyright.com 2014-06-29

# MyFreeCopyright.com: FREE Copyright Protection

## Privacy Policy

### Privacy Guarantee

Your copyright registrations will always be completed with confidentiality. Your name and information you provide will never be sold to marketing or direct-mail companies, and you will never be overwhelmed with mailings from us.

### Commitment to Your Privacy

This site is owned and operated by MyFreeCopyright.com, Inc. Your privacy is of the utmost importance to us and we want to make your experience with us satisfying and safe.

Since we do gather certain types of information about our users, we feel you should fully understand the terms and conditions surrounding the capture and use of that information. This privacy notice discloses what information we gather and how we may use it.

### Information MyFreeCopyright.com, Inc. May Gather and Track

  * Information that users provide through optional, voluntary submissions. For example, voluntary submissions to register a copyright, to receive our electronic newsletters or reports, to participate in our weblog or forums, to tell a friend, and from participation in polls and surveys, etc.
  * Information gathered through aggregated tracking information derived mainly by tallying page views throughout our site. This information allows us to better tailor our content to users' needs and to help us better understand the demographics of our audience. Under no circumstances does MyFreeCopyright.com, Inc. divulge any information about an individual user to a third party.

### MyFreeCopyright.com, Inc. May Gather User Information in the Following Processes:

**Optional Voluntary Information**  
We offer the following services, which require some type of voluntary submission of personal information by users:

  1. Copyright registrations

MyFreeCopyright.com, Inc. gathers email address, name, country, and password of users who voluntarily choose to use our services. Users will also be required to provide details of your copyright as well as submitting the copyright to be fingerprinted. Once fingerprinted, your copyright is permanently deleted and is kept safe during the fingerprinting process. At any time an account can be closed by contacting MyFreeCopyright.com, Inc.

  2. Electronic newsletters

MyFreeCopyright.com, Inc. gathers the name and email address of users who voluntarily subscribe. Users may remove themselves from this mailing list by following the link provided in every newsletter that points users to the subscription management page. Or, in the event no such link is provided, users may email MyFreeCopyright.com, Inc. requesting to be removed from this mailing list. Users can also subscribe to the newsletters at the time of registration.

  3. Weblog, forums, and email

Users of the site's Message Boards, Forums, Chat, and Email may be required to register separately for these services (all are free of charge) in order to post messages and/or use email, although they needn't register to visit the site. During registration the user is required to supply a password and email address.

  4. Polling and Reviews

We may offer interactive polls and customer reviews to users so they can easily share their opinions with other users and see what our audience thinks about important issues. Opinions or other responses to polls and reviews are aggregated and are not identifiable to any particular user. MyFreeCopyright.com, Inc. may use a system to "tag" users after they have voted or issued a review, so they can vote/review only once on a particular question/product. This tag is not correlated with information about individual users.

  5. Surveys

MyFreeCopyright.com, Inc. may occasionally conduct user surveys to better target our content to our audience. We never share any of this information about specific individuals with any third party.

  6. Contests

MyFreeCopyright.com, Inc. may occasionally offer promotional contests to our audience. When you enter a contest or other promotional feature, we may ask for identifying information such as your name and email address so we can administer the contest and notify winners. We never share any of this information about specific individuals with any third party.

  7. Upgrades

MyFreeCopyright.com, Inc. gathers name, address, country, credit card number and credit card expiration when a user chooses to upgrade their account from the free service. MyFreeCopyright.com, Inc. will not store this information and is only used during the process of billing. Our secure server has been approved by the merchant providers to be safe and compliant with the latest security measures to ensure your protection.

### Usage Tracking

MyFreeCopyright.com, Inc. tracks user traffic patterns throughout all of our site. However, we do not correlate this information with data about individual users. MyFreeCopyright.com, Inc. does break down overall usage statistics according to a user's domain name, browser type, and MIME type by reading this information from the browser string (information contained in every user's browser).

MyFreeCopyright.com, Inc. sometimes tracks and catalogs the search terms that users enter in our Search function, but this tracking is never associated with individual users. We use tracking information to determine which areas of our site users like and don't like based on traffic to those areas. We do not track what individual users read, but rather how well each page performs overall. This helps us continue to build a better service for you.

### Cookies

We may place a text file called a "cookie" in the browser files of your computer. The cookie itself does not contain Personal Information although it will enable us to relate your use of this site to information that you have specifically and knowingly provided. But the only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply yourself. A cookie can't read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites. MyFreeCopyright.com, Inc. uses cookies to track user traffic patterns (as described above).

You can refuse cookies by turning them off in your browser. If you've set your browser to warn you before accepting cookies, you will receive the warning message with each cookie. You do not need to have cookies turned on to use this site. However, you may need cookies to participate actively in weblog, forums, email, polling, reviews, surveys, etc.

### Use of Information

MyFreeCopyright.com, Inc. uses any information voluntarily given by our users to enhance their experience on our site, whether to provide interactive or personalized elements on the site or to better prepare future content based on the interests of our users.

As stated above, we use information that users voluntarily provide in order to send out electronic newsletters and to enable users to participate in weblog, forums, email, polling, reviews, surveys, etc. We send out newsletters to subscribers on a regular schedule (depending on the newsletter), and occasionally send out special editions when we think subscribers might be particularly interested in something we are doing. MyFreeCopyright.com, Inc. never shares newsletter mailing lists with any third parties, including advertisers, sponsors or partners.

We use tracking information to determine which areas of our site users like and don't like based on traffic to those areas. We do not track what individual users read, but rather how well each page performs overall. This helps us continue to build a better service for you. We track search terms entered in the Search function as one of many measures of what interests our users. But we don't track which terms a particular user enters.

MyFreeCopyright.com, Inc. creates aggregate reports on user demographics and traffic patterns. We will not disclose any information about any individual user except to (i) comply with applicable law or valid legal process, (ii) enforce or apply the terms of any of our user agreements or (iii) protect the rights, property or personal safety of MyFreeCopyright.com, Inc., our users, or the public.

### Sharing of the Information

MyFreeCopyright.com, Inc. uses the above-described information to tailor our content to suit your needs and help us better understand our audience's demographics. This is essential to keeping our service free. We will not share information about individual users with any third party, except to comply with applicable law or valid legal process or to protect the personal safety of our users or the public.

### Security

MyFreeCopyright.com, Inc. operates secure data networks protected by industry standard firewall and password protection systems. Our security and privacy policies are periodically reviewed and enhanced as necessary and only authorized individuals have access to the information provided by our customers.

### Opt-out Policy

We give users options wherever necessary and practical. Such choices include:

  * Opting not to register to receive our electronic newsletters.
  * Opting not to participate in certain interactive areas, which completely alleviates the need to gather any personally identifiable information from our users.
  * Opting not to display a users copyrights registration in the public domain.

### Your Consent

By using this site, you consent to the collection and use of this information by MyFreeCopyright.com, Inc. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.
